Wolff, Sidney A. Arbitration Files 5131
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Craftsmen Welders Inc. - Dupont. (Box 12)
  - Dairy Sealed, Inc. with Local 602, I.B.T., 1949 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Dannon Milk Products, Inc. with Local 602, I.BT., 1949 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Dash Metal Products Co. with Local 475 UERMWA, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Decorative Cabinet Corp. - Allied Union Local 92, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Debs Radio Memorial Fund Inc. with Radio and Television Broadcast Radio Station WEUD) Engineers Union, Local 1212, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Dumont Electric Corp. with Local 430, UE, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - De Pont De Nemours and Co. - Chain Workers Association Inc., 1956 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Eastern Novelty - Flight Foods. (Box 13)
  - El Mundo, Inc. - P.R. Newspaper Guild, Local 235, 1966-1968 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Electrol, Inc. - Local 1562, IAM, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Emerson Radio and Television Co. - Local 480 IUE - CIO, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Empire City Soft Drink Distributors) - Soft Drink Workers Local 812, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Faberge, Inc. with Local 121 United Chemical Workers of American Affiliates with Dist. 657, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Fairchild Engine Division Fairchild Engine + Airplane Corp. with Local 661, UAW, CIO, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Fairchild + Engine Division Fairchild Engine + Airplane Corp. with I.U.U.A.A.A.I.W.A., UAW - CIO, Local 661, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Fairchild Engine + Airplane Corp. UAW - CIO Local 661, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Fairchild Engine - Local 661 - UAW, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Stratos Div. Fairchild Engine - Lodge 893 - I.A.M., 1957-1958 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Fairchild Engine Div. - Local 661 UAW Am Arb., 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Fairchild Engine Div. - Local 661 AAA, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Fairsex Novelty Co. - Textile Workers NY Mediation Bd., 1959 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Fall River Textile Manufacturers Association New Bedford Cotton Manufacturers' Association with Textile Workers Union of America, CIO, 1952-1953 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Committee for Companies and Agents, Atlantic and Gulf Coasts Radio Officers with Radio Officers Union, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Feurer Brothers, Inc. - Local 147, Watch + Jewelry Workers, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Fields Baking Co. with Local 802, Bakery + Pastry Drivers Union, 1949-1950 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Fireside Inn, Inc. with Writer + Waitress Union, 1951 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Firestone Tire + Rubber, 1961-1963 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Firestone Tire + Rubber Co. Local 917 I.B.T., 1965 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Firestone Tire, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Five Star Hardware + Elec. Corp. - United Electronics Union Local 1507, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Flight Foods with Local 501, Air Transport Med. Bd., 1957 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Flushing News - Gimble Brothers. (Box 14)
  - Publishing News Company, Incorporated, Woodhaven News Company, Bukzin News Company, and Langer News Company against Newspaper and Mail Deliverers' Union of New York and Vicinity (Minutes: Hearings), 1941 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    February 10, 14, 1941. Bound.
  - Ford Instrument Company, Division of Sperry Rand Corporation, and Engineering, Technical, and Clerical Federation Local 471, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Fordham Glass Works, Incorporated versus Local 528, Glass Bevellers, Mirror Workers and Cutters Union, 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - International Association of Machinists versus Forstmann Woolen Company, 1956 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Frasetta Construction Company, Incorporated, and the United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, Local 964, 1965-1967 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Fugazy Continental, Incorporated, and the Amalgamated Local Union 355, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Fur Stylists Association with Fur Designers and Patternmakers Union, Local 120, 1950-1951 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Fur Stylists Association with Fur Designers and Patternmakers Union, Local 120 (Affiliated with the Furrier Joint Council, International Fur and Leather Workers Union), 1947-1948 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Wine and Liquor Store Employees Union, Local 122, and Kenneth Glaser, Gardner Liquors, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Gem Electric Manufacturing Company, Incorporated, with Local 475, United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1948-1949 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - General Electric - International Union of Electrical Workers, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - General Electric - International Union of Electrical Workers, 1959-1960 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - General Electric - International Union of Electrical Workers, 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - General Foods Corporation, Maxwell House Division, with Amalgamated Food and Allied Workers Union, Local 56 Case 54 A/537 (Pay for Certain Days), 1954 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Gimbels - Local 2, Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Employees, 1946 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Gimbels - Local 2, Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Employees (Wage Case), 1946 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Gimbels - Local 2, Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Employees (Wage Case_, 1946 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Gimbels - Local 2, Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Employees (Wage Case), 1946 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Union Exhibits 17-24 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Gimbels - Local 2, Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Employees (Wage Case), 1946 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Gimbels - Local 2, Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Employees (Union Exhibit 9), 1946 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Gimbels - Local 2, Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Employees (Minutes of Hearing), 1946 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    August 6, 1946. Bound.
  - Gimbels - Local 2, Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Employees (Agreements), 1947 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    December 16, 1947
  - Gimbels - Local 2, Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Employees, 1947 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Gimbels - District 65, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Gimbels - Local 2, Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Employees, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Gimbel Brothers, Incorporated, with District 65, Distributive, Processing, and Office Workers of America, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Gimbels - Local 2, Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Employees, 1947-1948 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Gimble Brothers - Gulf Oil Co.. (Box 15)
  - Gimbels - Local 2, Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Employees, 1946 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    August 14, 1946. Bound.
  - Gimbels - Local 2, Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Employees, 1946 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    August 20, 1946
  - Golden Seal Farms, Incorporated with Locals 757, 1121, Ice Cream Drivers and Employees Union, 1955-1957 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Gottfried Baking Company, Incorporated, with Local 802, Bakery and Pastry Drivers and Helpers Union, 1949-1950 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Gould-National Batteries, Incorporated and Industrial Union Local 210, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Gordon Baking Company - Local 802, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1947 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - The Gould Company (New York Employing Printers Association - New York Typographical Union 6), 1959 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Grand Union Company - Local 456, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Grandview Dairy Arbitration (File 1), 1939 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Grandview Dairy Arbitration (File 2), 1939 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Gussie Stark and the Great American Indemnity Company, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers, Local 282, and the Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Greater New York Photo Finishing Association, Incorporated, and Local 415, United Photographic Employees Union, 1938-1952 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Greater New York Umbrella Manufacturers, Incorporated and Textile Workers Union of America, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Gulf Oil Corporation - Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers of America, 1957-1958 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Gulf Oil Corporation and Petroleum Trades Employee Union, Incorporated, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Hadassah Women's Zionist Org. - Harmony Wine and Liquor. (Box 16)
  - Hadassah Women's Zionist Organization Local 19, 1947 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Hale Associates with United Office + Professional Workers of America, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Hamilton Milk + Cream Co., Inc., 1962 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Hammarland Mfg. Co. with Local 475. IUE CIO, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Hampton Looms of Virginia, Inc. with Local 358, T.W.U.A., C.I.O., 1955 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Handy + Harmon - Ud. Steelworkers, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Hanscom with Local 50 Bakery and Confectionery Union AFL, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Hanscom Baking Corp. with Local 50, Bakery and Confectionery Workers International Union of America, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Harmony Wine + Liquor Inc. - Local 177 Wine + Liquor State Employees, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Hathaway - Huron Corporation. (Box 17)
  - Hathaway Manufacturing Company -and- Textile Workers Union of America, CIO, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Hathaway Manufacturing Company, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Hathaway Minutes of Hearing Exhibits, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Health Insurance Plan with Local 153, U.O.P.W.A., 1954 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - W.S. Hein and Co. Mediation Board, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Hedstrom Union Co. United Furn. Workers, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Helena Rubenstein, Inc. Oil Chemical + Atomic Workers - Amer. Arb., 1957 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Hercules Wrecking Company with Local 95, House Wreckers, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Hewitt-Robins Inc. United Rubber Local 584, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Hewett-Robins - I.A.M. Dist. A-16, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Hillside Housing Corporation Local 3vE B.S.E. -I.U. -AFL-, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Hilton Marwell Company Local 65, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Home Richardson Scale Co. - District 15, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Hudson + Manhattan Railroad National Adjustment Board, 1958-1959 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Independent Theatre Owners - Junior Leasing Corporation. (Box 18)
  - Independent Theatre Owners Assn. Local 306 Motion Picture Operators Wage, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Industrial Rayon Corp. - Local 202 Textile Workers, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Industrial Rayon - Covington Va. T.W.U., 1955 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Industrial Rayon Corporation with T.W.U., 1955 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Interlock Metal - Amalgamated Meat Cutters, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - International Harvester Co. Local, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - International Harvester Company with District Number 15, I.A.M., 1956-1957 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Interscience Publishing Co. with Greater New York Local Book and Magazine Division, U.O.P.W.A., 1951 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Island Pines Inc. (RSUP) with Local 15, Bartenders Union, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Jacob Ruppert - Brewery + Local 1345 (Teamsters) (AAA), 1949 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Jacobs Co., Inc. - Loc. 810, I.B.T., 1964-1965 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Jamaica Water Supply - Utility Workers Union - AAA, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Jamaica Water Supply Co. Utility Workers, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Jamaica Brass Mfg. Co. with Local 1146, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Jersey Journal - Jersey City Typo Union No. 94 - AAA, 1956-1960 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Jewish Child Care Association w. Social Service Workers WL-67, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Jewish Child Care Assn. - Social Service Workers, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Joelson Circuit - Local 306 Moving Picture Maebline Operators Union, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - John Edwards Company w. Local 138 I.B.T., 1947 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - John Hancock Mut. Life Ins. - Ins. Workers International Union, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - John Hancock Mutual Life Insurance Co. w- U.O.P.W.A., 1948 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - John Hancock Life - I.W.I.U. - Amer. Arb. Closed. WL. 412, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - John-Manville Products Corp. Federal Labor Union AAA, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Johnson Belting Co. - Leather Workers of Greater N.Y. Local 35, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Journal News Corp. - Newspaper Guild -, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Joy Manufacturing Company - Dist. 72, I.A.M., 1969 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Trinity Church Arbitration, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Mack Truck U.A.W., 1952-1953 (Box 18, Folder 28)
- K.L.M. - M.G.M.. (Box 19)
  - KLM Royal Dutch Airlines - Transportation Workers Union, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Karp Company - Local 150, United Mechanics, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Keeler's State Dining, Incorporated and Local 471, Hotel, Motel, Restaurant Employees and Bartenders Union (Overtime and Weekly Wage Rate), 1965- 1966 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Jimmy Kelly's Restaurant with the Waiters and Waitresses Union, Local 1, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Kentile, Incorporated - Local 457, United Rubber Workers (Lunch and Rest Periods), 1964 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Kentile, Incorporated, with Local 457, United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America, 1955-1957 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Kentile, Incorporated, with the United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America, Local 457 (failure to discharge four employees), 1956 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Kidde Manufacturing Company - Local 437, United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1948-1949 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Kidde Manufacturing Company, Incorporated, with Local 437, United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America (Suspension of W. Martin), 1955 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - King's Automatic Plating Company with International Union of Electrical Workers, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - King's Electronics Company, Incorporated, and Local 475, United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Kleinert Rubber Company - American Federation of Rubber Workers Local 20499, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Ford Company - International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 277, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Kreis, Maurice M. with Seaman, Milton, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - A. Kriemer, Incorporated with Local 475, United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Kudner Agency and American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (Violation of provision of CBA requiring mechanical reproduction from live performances only), 1955-1958 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Labor Standards Association (Pittsburgh) - Local 101, United Department Store Employees Union - Local 1365, Retail Clerks International Association, 1950 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Labor Standards Association (Pittsburgh) - Local 101, United Department Store Employees Union - Local 1365, Retail Clerks International Association, 1948- 1950 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Labor Standards Association (Pittsburgh) - Local 101, United Department Store Employees Union - Local 1365, Retail Clerks International Association, 1948- 1950 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - La Belle Silver Company, Incorporated - Local 475, United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, 1948-1949 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Lambert Pharmacal Company - United Packinghouse Workers of America, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - M.H. Lazarus and Company, Incorporated - Local 65, Wholesale and Warehouse Workers Union, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - League of New York Theatres - Association of Theatrical Press Agents and Managers, 1956 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Lever Brothers Company - Local 51, International Chemical Workers Union (Reassignment), 1965 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Liberty Products Corporation with Liberty Lodge 1767, International Association of Machinists, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Liebmann Breweries, Incorporated - United Brewery, Flour, and Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers of America, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Liebmann Breweries - Local 46, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Linden Boxcraft Corporation - Local 299, Paper Box Makers Union, 1947-1948 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Little Venice Restaurant - Local 1, Waiters and Waitresses Union, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Screen Office and Professional Employees Guild Local 109 - Loew's Incorporated, MGM International Films Corporation, Marcus Loew Booking Agency, Loew's International Corporation, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Screen Office and Professional Employees Guild Local 109 - Loew's Incorporated, MGM International Films Corporation, Marcus Loew Booking Agency, Loew's International Corporation, 1942-1949 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Long Island Outfitting Company - Local 830, Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Employees, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Lycoming Division, Avco Manufacturing Company - United Automobile Workers Local 1010, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - MGM Telestudios, Incorporated - Local 1212, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 34)
- Mack Truck - Midtown Realty. (Box 20)
  - Mack Manufacturing Corp. U.A.W. Am Arb. Assn., 1958 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Mack Manufacturing Corp. Local 229 U.A.W., 1955 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Mackay Radio and Telegraph Company with American Communications Association, 1948 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - NACYS - Local 18 - RWDSU Amer. Arb., 1959 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Madison Dining Room Inc. - Local Jt. Ec. Board, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Maidman Properties Inc. with Local 144, Hotel Front Service Employees (90 Standish Hotel), 1950 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Manhattan Marine Company with Local 1146. A.F.L., 1953 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Manhattan Center - Waiter + Waitresses Union - No. 1 Med. Bd., 1948 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Manhattan News, Co. Inc. with Local 917, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, AFL, 1948 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Manhattan Novelty Corp. with District 65, RWDSU, CIO, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Marinette Paper co. (Scott Paper) United Wine Workers, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Edward B. Marks Music Publishing with Frank Hennigs, 1948 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Mark Can Corp. with Local 475 UERMWA, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Glen Martin Company Co., 1964 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Marvel Slide Fastener Corp. with Local 475 UERMWA, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Masters' Electro-Plating Assn. Inc. - Metal Polishers - Local 118 Mediation Board, 1946-1947 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - W.L. Maxson Corp. - U.A.W. - Local 1221 - AAA, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - McInerney Spring and Wire with Local 700, UAW Company, 1951 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - McKiernan + Terry with District No. 47, I.A.M., 1953-1954 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Merchants Bank of New York with Financial Emp. Guild, Local 96 - CIO, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Merkel, Inc. - Local 174. Butcher's Union, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Mercer Upholstering Corp. with Local 76-13 U.F.W.A., 1948 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Merck + Company Inc. (Chemical Division_ with Local 515, United Gas, Coke + Chemical Workers, CIO, 1954 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Metropolitan Plywood Distributors - Local 138 I.B.T., 1957 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Metropolitan Funeral Directors Assn. with Local 21381 Embalmers Union, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Metropolitan Funeral Director with Licensed Embalmers Union of Greater New York, Local 21381, AFL, 1949 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Metropolitan Jockey Club with Independent Association of Mutual Employees of New York State, 1950-1961 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Metropolitan Roll + Pastry Association - Bakers Union Local 1, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Metropolitan Window Cleaning Co. Local 1 Window Chances Union, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Midtown Reality Owners' Association, Inc. with Local 164 Building Service Employees National Union AFL, 1951 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Midtown Realty Owners' Association, Inc. with Local 164 Building Service Employees International Union AFL, 1950 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Midtown Realty Arbitration, 1940 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Midtown Realty Owners Association, Inc., 1950 (Box 20, Folder 33)
- Miller Motor Express - New Jersey Bell Telephone Company. (Box 21)
  - Miller Motor Express - Local 802, Truck Drivers and Chauffeurs, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Mohawk Airlines, Incorporated - Air Line Pilots Association, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Mohawk Airlines, Incorporated - Air Line Pilots Association, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Morgen's Restaurant - Dining Room Employees, Local 1, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Mutual Drug Sundry Company, Incorporated - Allied Trades Council, 1950 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - NBC (National Broadcasting Company) - Mellolarks, 1959-1960 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - N. Sumergarde and Sons, Incorporated - Local 444, Textile Workers Union of America, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Namm's - Local 1250, Department Store Employees Union, 1949-1950 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Nash Plaza Motors Incorporated - United Auto Workers Local 259, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Nashawena Mills - Textile Workers Union of America, 1952 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Nassau Smelting and Refining Company - Local 729, United Steelworkers of America, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - National Cash Register Company - National Cash Register Employees' Independent Union, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - National Metal Art Company - Local 475, AMI and MWU, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - National Railroad Adjustment Board - Third Division, 1957-1959 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - National Silver Warehouse Company - Local 65, Wholesale and Warehouse Workers Union, 1948-1951 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Athenia Steel Division, National Standard Company - United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1962 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - NAUMKEAG Steam Cotton Company - Textile Workers Union of America, 1952 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Nereid Bakery - Local 1111, Bakery and Confectionery Workers, 1947-1948 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - New Bedford Cotton Manufacturers Association, 1944-1948 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    Bound. February 19, 1944-December 1948
  - New Bedford Cotton Manufacturers Association, 1949-1951 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    January 1, 1949-December 1951
  - New Broadcasting Company Incorporated - American Communications Association, 1951-1952 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - New Jersey Bell Telephone Company - Telephone Workers Union of New Jersey, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - New Jersey Bell Telephone Company - Telephone Workers Union of New Jersey, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    June 3, 1954. Bound.
  - New Jersey Bell Telephone Company - Telephone Workers Union of New Jersey, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    July 2, 1954. Bound.
- Neo Gravure Printing Company - New York Wholesale Grocers. (Box 22)
  - Neo Gravure Printing Company - Local 20940, American Federation of Office Employees, 1947 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - New York and Pennsylvania Company - Local 701, United Papermakers and Paperworkers, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - New York and Pennsylvania Company, Incorporated - United Papermakers and Paperworkers Local 701, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    Includes several photographs of New York and Pennsylvania Company
  - New York and Pennsylvania Company (Lock Haven, Pennsylvania) - United Papermakers and Paperworkers Local 787, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - New York Caterers Trade Association - Local 89, Chefs, Cooks, Pastry Cooks, and Assistants Union, 1956-1957 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - New York Distributors - Allied Trades Council, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - New York Merchandise Company - Local 65, Wholesale, Retail, and Warehouse Workers Union, 1950 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - New York Merchandise Company, Incorporated - District 65, Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York - New York Post, 1950 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York - New York Post, 1946-1950 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper Guild of New York - New York Post, 1947 (Box 22, Folder 11)